<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Brawl Wiki</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <!-- Nav Drawer Menu Strings -->
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_players">Players</string>
    <string name="menu_brawlers">Brawlers</string>
    <string name="menu_clubs">Clubs</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="menu_profile_settings">Profile Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_brawler_details">Brawler Details</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>



    <!-- Ad Banner Strings -->
    <string name="banner_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>

    <!-- Brawler Description -->
    <string name="description_shelly">Shelly\'s spread-fire shotgun blasts the other team with
        buckshot. Her Super destroys cover and keeps her opponents at a distance!</string>
    <string name="description_bit">8-BIT lumbers along like an arcade cabinet on legs. He shoots
        Blaster Beams and his Super boosts friendlies\' damage!</string>
    <string name="description_colt">Colt fires an accurate burst of bullets from his dual revolvers.
        His Super shreds cover and extends the bullet barrage!</string>
    <string name="description_bull">Bull deals massive damage up close with his shotgun. For his
        Super move, he charges through barriers and knocks back enemies!</string>
    <string name="description_nita">Nita strikes her enemies with a thunderous shockwave. Her Super
        summons a massive bear to fight by her side!</string>
    <string name="description_dynamike">Dynamike lobs two explosive sticks of dynamite. His Super
        attack is a whole barrel full of dynamite that blows up cover!</string>
    <string name="description_bo">Bo fires three explosive arrows toward his targets. His Super ability
        places a trio of hidden, explosive mines on the ground!</string>
    <string name="description_emz">Emz attacks with blasts of hair spray that deal damage over time, and
        slows down opponents with her Super.</string>
    <string name="description_jessie">Jessie\'s Shock Rifle shoots energy orbs that bounce between enemies.
        Her Super deploys a cute but deadly gun turret!</string>
    <string name="description_brock">Brock fires a long-range, explosive rocket at enemies. His Super is a
        ballistic rocket barrage that destroys cover!</string>
    <string name="description_rosa">This boxing botanist will plant her feet and go toe to toe! Her Super gives
        her tough, vegan protective gear.</string>
    <string name="description_primo">El Primo throws a flurry of punches at his enemies. His Super is a leaping
        elbow drop that deals damage to all caught underneath!</string>
    <string name="description_poco">Poco fires damaging sound waves at enemies. His Super can heal both Poco
        himself and his teammates!</string>
    <string name="description_barley">Barley attacks by lobbing bottles at enemies, doing splash damage. His
        Super is a huge barrage of burning bottles!</string>
    <string name="description_jacky">Jacky works her Jackhammer to shake up the ground and nearby enemies.
        Her Super pulls in nearby foes, leaving them in the dust!</string>
    <string name="description_darryl">Jacky works her Jackhammer to shake up the ground and nearby enemies.
        Her Super pulls in nearby foes, leaving them in the dust!</string>
    <string name="description_rico">Rico fires a burst of bullets that bounce off walls. His Super burst is
        a long barrage of bouncy bullets that pierce targets!</string>
    <string name="description_carl">Carl throws his Pickaxe like a boomerang. His Super is a crazy cart spin
        that clobbers anyone around him.</string>
    <string name="description_penny">Penny shoots bags of coins, damaging the target and anyone standing behind.
        Her Super is a mortar-style cannon turret!</string>
    <string name="description_piper">Piper\'s sniper shots do more damage the farther they travel. Her Super drops
        grenades at her feet, while Piper herself leaps away!</string>
    <string name="description_bibi">Batter up! Bibi\'s got a sweet swing that can knock back enemies when her Home
        Run bar is charged. Her Super is a bouncing ball of gum that deals damage.</string>
    <string name="description_bea">Bea loves bugs and hugs. She shoots her mechanical drones at range, and her Super
        sends forth an angry army of swarming bees!</string>
    <string name="description_nani">Nani loves her friends and looks over them with a watchful lens. She handles threats
        with angled shots, and her Super allows Nani to commandeer her pal Peep, who goes out with a bang!</string>
    <string name="description_frank">Frank swings his hammer at enemies, sending a shockwave. His Super is an especially
        powerful blow that stuns enemies!</string>
    <string name="description_pam">Pam shoots from the hip, peppering targets with shrapnel. Her Super is a healing turret
        that restores her and teammates\' health!</string>
    <string name="description_max">Max goes fast! Her attack is a fast-firing blaster. Her Super speeds up her and allies!</string>
    <string name="description_mortis">Mortis dashes forward with each swing of his shovel. As his Super attack, he sends
        a cloud of bats to damage enemies and heal himself!</string>
    <string name="description_sprout">Sprout was built to plant life, launching bouncy Seed Bombs with reckless love. Its Super
        creates a plant-based obstacle!</string>
    <string name="description_gene">Gene uses his magic lamp to shoot a splitting projectile. His super is a magical hand that
        grabs and pulls enemies close!</string>
    <string name="description_tick">Tick is a metal ball of barely controlled excitement and energy - explosive energy! He throws
        mines, and his Super makes his head detach, seek a target and explode.</string>
    <string name="description_tara">Tara\'s triple tarot card attack pierces through enemies. Her Super is a black hole that
        sucks in all nearby enemies, causing damage!</string>
    <string name="description_mrp">Mr. P is a disgruntled luggage handler who angrily hurls suitcases at opponents. His Super
        calls robo-porters to help him.</string>
    <string name="description_amber">Amber has always been a firebug. She loves to light up the world and any opponents that
        come at her!</string>
    <string name="description_leon">Leon shoots a quick salvo of blades at his target. His Super trick is a smoke bomb that
        makes him invisible for a little while!</string>
    <string name="description_crow">Crow fires a trio of poisoned daggers. As a Super move he leaps, firing daggers both on
        jump and on landing!</string>
    <string name="description_spike">Spike throws cactus grenades that send needles flying, and a show-stopping Super: a field of
        cactus spines that slows down and damages enemies!</string>
    <string name="description_sandy">Sandy is a sleep-deprived Brawler with powerful control over sand: casting sharp pebbles at
        enemies, and summoning a sandstorm to hide teammates.</string>
    <string name="description_colette">Colette is going to get you! She taxes opponents\' health and has fancy moves to boot.</string>
    <string name="description_surge">He\'s a Protector with a penchant for parties. Surge attacks foes with energy drink
        blasts that split in 2 on contact. His Super upgrades his stats in 3 stages and comes complete with totally awesome Body mods!</string>
    <string name="description_gale">Gale is a tireless handyman who gets no rest. With his blower, he blasts foes with a wide shot of
        wind and snow, while his Super pushes them back with a forceful blizzard!</string>

    <!-- StarPower descriptions -->
    <string name="star_shelly_one">Shelly\'s Super shells slow down enemies for 3.0 seconds!</string>
    <string name="star_shelly_two">When Shelly falls below 40% health, she instantly heals for 1800 health. Band-Aid recharges in 20.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="star_nita_one">Nita recovers 500 health whenever her bear hits an enemy. When Nita deals damage, her bear regains 500 health.</string>
    <string name="star_nita_two">Nita\'s bear attacks faster. Time between swipes is reduced by 60%.</string>
    <string name="star_colt_one">Colt\'s movement speed is increased by 10%.</string>
    <string name="star_colt_two">Colt’s main attack range and bullet speed are increased by 11%.</string>
    <string name="star_bull_one">When Bull falls below 40% health, his reload speed doubles!</string>
    <string name="star_bull_two">When Bull falls below 40% health, he gains a shield that reduces all damage taken by 30%.</string>
    <string name="star_jessie_one">Jessie can repair her gun turret for 800 of its missing health by zapping it with her attack.</string>
    <string name="star_jessie_two">Scrappy the Turret now shoots energy orbs that bounce between enemies. The orbs\' range after a bounce is 51% of normal range.</string>
    <string name="star_brock_one">The impact of Brock\'s attack sets the ground on fire. Enemies in the area take 600 damage per second! Lasts for 2 seconds.</string>
    <string name="star_brock_two">Brock loads a fourth rocket into his launcher, increasing his ammo capacity (and discarding the thermos bottle he\'s been keeping in his launcher\'s #4 rube).</string>
    <string name="star_dynamike_one">Dynamike can ride the blast wave of his explosives to jump over obstacles!</string>
    <string name="star_dynamike_two">Adds +1000 damage to Mike’s Super.</string>
    <string name="star_bo_one">Bo spots enemies hidden in bushes from 150% longer distance than normally.</string>
    <string name="star_bo_two">Instead of a knockback, Bo’s traps now stun the enemy for 2.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="star_tick_one">When Tick takes no damage and doesn\'t attack, he starts recovering health 2.0 seconds faster than normal.</string>
    <string name="star_tick_two">Tick\'s reload time is 10% shorter.</string>
    <string name="star_bit_one">Increases the Damage Booster\'s range by 50%.</string>
    <string name="star_bit_two">When 8-Bit is near his Damage Booster, he will plug in and have increased movement speed.</string>
    <string name="star_emz_one">Enemies that stay within the cloud of Emz\'s toxic hair spray suffer increasing damage, 20% per hit.</string>
    <string name="star_emz_two">Emz recovers 300 health per second for each enemy inside her Super\'s area of effect.</string>
    <string name="star_primo_one">Enemies caught in El Primo\'s Super will burn for 1200 damage over 4 seconds.</string>
    <string name="star_primo_two">El Primo gains 25% speed boost for 4.0 seconds after using Super.</string>
    <string name="star_barley_one">Barley regains 400 health from each attack.</string>
    <string name="star_barley_two">Adds +140 damage per second to Barley’s attack.</string>
    <string name="star_poco_one">When Poco\'s attack hits friendly Brawlers they now heal for 700 health.</string>
    <string name="star_poco_two">Poco’s Super now also hits enemies, dealing 800 damage.</string>
    <string name="star_rosa_one">Rosa recovers 200 health per second when inside a bush.</string>
    <string name="star_rosa_two">Rosa’s punches gain +220 damage during her Super.</string>
    <string name="star_rico_one">Rico\'s bullets, from attack and Super alike, get supercharged by their first bounce and deal +100 damage!</string>
    <string name="star_rico_two">When Rico falls below 40% health, he runs 34% faster.</string>
    <string name="star_darryl_one">Darryl\'s Super reinforces his barrel, reducing all damage he takes by 30% for 0.9 seconds.</string>
    <string name="star_darryl_two">When Darryl uses his Super, he doubles his reload speed for 5.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="star_penny_one">When Penny\'s Cannon is destroyed, it shoots out one last barrage of 4 bombs targeting nearby enemies, each dealing 1680 damage.</string>
    <string name="star_penny_two">Cannonballs from Penny’s turret set the ground on fire for 3 seconds. Enemies in the burning area take 400 damage per second.</string>
    <string name="star_carl_one">Carl throws his Pickaxe with 13% more speed, allowing it to travel faster and return faster.</string>
    <string name="star_carl_two">During Carl\'s Super, all damage he receives is reduced by 30%.</string>
    <string name="star_jacky_one">When receiving damage, Jacky returns the favor by converting 15% of the damage into a Groundbreaker counterattack.</string>
    <string name="star_jacky_two">Jacky\'s Hard Hat protects her by reducing any damage she takes by 15%.</string>
    <string name="star_piper_one">Piper\'s attack deals +800 extra damage (at max range) when she\'s hidden in a bush.</string>
    <string name="star_piper_two">When Piper hits an enemy with her attack, she reloads 0.3 ammo instantly.</string>
    <string name="star_pam_one">Whenever Pam hits enemies with Scrapstorm, she heals herself and nearby friendly Brawlers for 40 health.</string>
    <string name="star_pam_two">Healing turret now also damages enemies for 500 damage per second.</string>
    <string name="star_frank_one">Frank steals the power of a Brawler he defeats, increasing his damage by 50% for 12 seconds!</string>
    <string name="star_frank_two">Frank gains +1100 health.</string>
    <string name="star_bibi_one">Bibi\'s movement speed is increased by 12% when her Home Run bar is fully charged.</string>
    <string name="star_bibi_two">When Bibi’s Homerun bar is fully charged, she shields herself from all damage by 30%.</string>
    <string name="star_bea_one">Instantly supercharge Bea\'s Big Sting one time if she misses a supercharged shot.</string>
    <string name="star_bea_two">Bea escapes certain defeat with 1 health, and gains a momentary shield once per match.</string>
    <string name="star_nani_one">Peep deals up to 2500 extra damage based on his travel distance.</string>
    <string name="star_nani_two">Nani takes 80% less damage while her Super is active.</string>
    <string name="star_mortis_one">Mortis reaps the life essence of Brawler he defeats, restoring 1800 of his health.</string>
    <string name="star_mortis_two">Mortis gains a Dash Bar! His dash range is increased by 75% when the bar is fully charged. It takes 3.5 seconds for the bar to charge when Mortis has all three dashes ready.</string>
    <string name="star_tara_one">Tara\'s Super cracks open a dimensional portal! A shadowy version of Tara appears and attacks her enemies.</string>
    <string name="star_tara_two">Tara’s Super cracks open a dimensional portal! A shadowy version of Tara’s appears to heal Tara and her teammates.</string>
    <string name="star_gene_one">Gene heals all friendly Brawlers around him for 400 health per second.</string>
    <string name="star_gene_two">When Gene\'s Super is fully charged he does +300 damage with his attack.</string>
    <string name="star_max_one">Max now charges her Super while moving.</string>
    <string name="star_max_two">Max reloads faster while moving.</string>
    <string name="star_mrp_one">Mr.P\'s overstuffed suitcases bounce and burst even if they don\'t hit a target or obstacle.</string>
    <string name="star_mrp_two">The robo-porters respawn 3 seconds faster after being defeated.</string>
    <string name="star_sprout_one">Seed Bombs that don\'t make contact with enemies will explode with a larger explosion radius.</string>
    <string name="star_sprout_two">Sprout activates a shield, partially protecting itself from all attacks while inside a bush.</string>
    <string name="star_spike_one">After using Super, Spike regenerates 800 health per second by staying in its area of effect.</string>
    <string name="star_spike_two">Spikes from cactus grenade fly in a curving motion, making it easier to hit targets.</string>
    <string name="star_crow_one">Crow\'s poison saps the strength of enemies, who deal 20% less damage while poisoned.</string>
    <string name="star_crow_two">Crow deals +120 damage with his attack and Super to targets with 50% or less health.</string>
    <string name="star_leon_one">When Leon uses his Super, he gains 24% boost to his movement speed for the duration of his invisibility.</string>
    <string name="star_leon_two">Leon recovers 1000 health per second while his Super is active.</string>
    <string name="star_sandy_one">Sandstorm now also damages enemies for 120 damage per second.</string>
    <string name="star_sandy_two">Sandstorm now also heals friendly Brawlers for 250 health per second.</string>
    <string name="star_amber_one">Amber can have two fuel puddles on the ground simultaneously and she will recharge her Super automatically when standing near one.</string>
    <string name="star_gale_one">Gale\'s Super now stuns enemies that are pushed against obstacles from his Super.</string>
    <string name="star_gale_two">Gale\'s snow balls now also slow down opponents for 0.3 seconds.</string>
    <string name="star_surge_one">Surge\'s main attack now splits when hitting walls or when reaching max distance.</string>
    <string name="star_surge_two">Surge keeps his STAGE 1 Super upgrade for the full match duration.</string>
    <string name="star_colette_one">All enemy brawlers hit by Colette\'s charge are carried to the farthest point of the attack!</string>
    <string name="star_colette_two">Colette\'s super gives her a 10% shield for 5.0 seconds. Every enemy brawler hit by it will add 10% more protection.</string>

    <!-- Gadget descriptions -->
    <string name="gadget_shelly_one">Shelly dashes ahead, skipping a few unnecessary steps!</string>
    <string name="gadget_shelly_two">On activation, Shelly\'s next main attack focuses the fire to a smaller area and increases the range.</string>
    <string name="gadget_nita_one">Nita commands her bear to slam the ground, stunning all enemies within its reach.</string>
    <string name="gadget_colt_one">Colt instantly reloads 2 ammo.</string>
    <string name="gadget_bull_one">Bull instantly rejuvenates himself for 1500 health.</string>
    <string name="gadget_bull_two">Bull can interrupt his Super charge and slow all nearby opponents with a massive stomp for 1.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_jessie_one">Jessie triggers a shockwave from her turret, slowing down all enemies within its area of effect.</string>
    <string name="gadget_jessie_two">Scrappy\'s attack speed is doubled for 5.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_brock_one">Brock blasts the ground below him and propels himself into the air. The explosion deals 500 damage to nearby enemies.</string>
    <string name="gadget_dynamike_one">Dynamike spins furiously and throws multiple sticks of dynamite around himself. Each dynamite deals 700 damage to enemies.</string>
    <string name="gadget_dynamike_two">Once activated, the next main attack also stuns enemies for 1.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_bo_one">Bo drops a totem that recharges his and any allies\' Supers within the area of effect.</string>
    <string name="gadget_bo_two">Bo triggers all of his mines instantly.</string>
    <string name="gadget_tick_one">Tick makes a quick dash, leaving a single mine on the ground.</string>
    <string name="gadget_bit_one">8-Bit instantly teleports to his Damage Booster.</string>
    <string name="gadget_emz_one">EMZ pushes back all enemies around her while also dealing 500 damage.</string>
    <string name="gadget_primo_one">El Primo grabs the closest enemy within his reach and flips them like a pancake over his broad shoulders.</string>
    <string name="gadget_primo_two">El Primo summons a small meteor to strike the nearest enemy. It deals 2000 damage and destroys walls.</string>
    <string name="gadget_barley_one">Barley drops a sticky concoction that leaves a puddle, slowing down all enemies that make contact with it.</string>
    <string name="gadget_barley_two">Barley throws a healing potion at nearby allies that creates an area that heals for 500 health per second.</string>
    <string name="gadget_poco_one">Poco and all nearby allies heal 500 health per second for 5.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_rosa_one">Rosa fertilizes the ground around her and bushes instantly grow to provide great cover.</string>
    <string name="gadget_rico_one">Rico blasts waves of bouncy bullets in all directions.</string>
    <string name="gadget_darryl_one">Darryl spins around and sprays a barrage of shots in all directions. Each shot deals 400 damage and recharges his Super by 25% if it hits enemies!</string>
    <string name="gadget_darryl_two">Darryl creates a slowing area around himself for 4.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_penny_one">Penny blows up her cannon! The explosion destroys walls and deals 1500 damage to nearby enemies.</string>
    <string name="gadget_penny_two">Penny calls an artillery strike from her Cannon to her current location.</string>
    <string name="gadget_carl_one">Carl drops a trail of hot rocks behind his cart! The rocks deal 300 damage per second to enemies who step on them.</string>
    <string name="gadget_jacky_one">Jacky gets a burst of energy and moves 20% faster for 3.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_piper_one">Piper pops a defensive shot at the closest enemy, dealing 100 damage, while also pushing them back and slowing them down.</string>
    <string name="gadget_piper_two">On activation, Piper\'s next main attack will home in on enemies.</string>
    <string name="gadget_pam_one">Pam triggers her turret to emit a pulse that heals allies inside the turret\'s range, including herself, for 1200 health.</string>
    <string name="gadget_frank_one">Frank clears any disabling effect on himself, and momentarily becomes immune to stuns, slows and knockbacks.</string>
    <string name="gadget_bibi_one">Bibi heals 600 health per second for 4.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_bea_one">Bea drops a beehive with a splash of sticky honey around it. The honey slows down enemies that step in it.</string>
    <string name="gadget_bea_two">Bea unleashes 3 angry bees that circle away from her, dealing more damage the further they go (up to 1000 damage).</string>
    <string name="gadget_nani_one">Nani detonates Peep and teleports herself to his last location.</string>
    <string name="gadget_mortis_one">Mortis spins his shovel, hitting all enemies around himself for 1300 damage.</string>
    <string name="gadget_mortis_two">Mortis reloads faster for 4.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_tara_one">Tara and her allies are able to see all enemies, even inside bushes, for 5.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_gene_one">All enemies close to Gene are instantly pushed back. Gene also restores 700 health.</string>
    <string name="gadget_max_one">Max dashes forward, and becomes immune to all damage from enemies while dashing.</string>
    <string name="gadget_max_two">Max blinks back to a place of her choosing after 4.0 seconds\' delay, recovering any damage she received in the meantime.</string>
    <string name="gadget_mrp_one">Mr. P buffs his current porter by increasing its damage by 150 and health by 1000.</string>
    <string name="gadget_sprout_one">Sprout consumes a bush to restore 2000 health.</string>
    <string name="gadget_spike_one">Spike shoots 3 waves of needles in all directions, dealing 520 damage per hit.</string>
    <string name="gadget_crow_one">Crow gets a shield for 60% of incoming damage for 3.0 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_crow_two">All currently poisoned enemies are slowed for 2.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="gadget_leon_one">Leon creates an illusion of himself to confuse his enemies.</string>
    <string name="gadget_sandy_one">Sandy falls a sleep for 2.0 seconds and his health is fully restored.</string>
    <string name="gadget_amber_one">Amber runs fast for 3.0 seconds while spilling her fire fluid, which she can then ignite.</string>
    <string name="gadget_gale_one">Gale drops a bounce pad underfoot, launching friend and foe alike into the air.</string>
    <string name="gadget_surge_one">Surge overloads his circuits and teleports a short distance forward.</string>
    <string name="gadget_colette_one">Colette\'s next shot deals 40% of her current health as damage.</string>

    <!-- About Settings -->
    <string name="settings_about">BrawlWiki is your open source to all the content available in Brawl Stars to provide
        you with a fun experience to get a better understanding of your personal stats, past/present game modes, and
        all brawlers currently available in the game, and top rankings of players/clubs across the globe! \n\nThe app will
        be updated at a steady pace to provide you with the best stats/information and new content. </string>

    <!-- My token -->
    <string name="my_token">MyToken</string>

    <!-- My tag -->
    <string name="my_tag">MyTag</string>

    <!-- Brawl stars API url -->
    <string name="brawl_stars_api_url">https://developer.brawlstars.com/#/</string>

    <!-- Login -->
    <string name="enter_token">Please enter a token</string>

    <!-- Error toast -->
    <string name="toast_error">Please check the status of error: \u0020</string>

    <!-- UI strings -->

        <!-- Settings Fragment -->
            <!-- Toast messages -->
            <string name="settings_token_reminder">Please enter your token to access brawl stars data</string>
            <string name="settings_tag_missing">Tag is missing. Please input your tag on home screen</string>
            <string name="settings_token_missing">Token is missing. Please input your token on initial screen</string>
                <!--Profile settings Fragment-->
                <string name="hash_tag">#</string>
                <string name="tag_not_set">No tag is set</string>
                <string name="token_not_set">No token is set</string>
                <string name="token_is_set">Token is set</string>
        <!-- Player Fragment -->
        <string name="bearer">Bearer \u0020</string>

        <!-- Home Fragment -->
        <string name="percentage">%</string>
        <string name="bundle_tag">tag</string>
        <string name="firebase_tag_key">FirebaseKey</string>

    <!-- Profile Fragment -->
            <string name="player_hash_tag">#</string>
            <string name="player_serializable">brawler_stat</string>

    <!-- Image description -->
        <!-- Star power list item -->
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_star_power_list">Image of a brawlers star power</string>

    <!-- Profile list item -->
        <string name="trophy_count_for_brawler">Trophy count for brawler</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_brawler">Image of a brawler</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_gadget">Image of a brawlers gadget</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_star_power">Image of a brawlers star power</string>

        <!-- Profile app widget -->
        <string name="image_of_a_users_icon">Image of a users icon</string>
        <string name="trophy_count_for_a_user">Trophy count for a user</string>

        <!-- Players list item -->
        <string name="image_of_a_players_icon">Image of a players icon</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_players_trophies">Image of a players trophies</string>

        <!-- Nav header main -->
        <string name="navigation_header_image_of_brawl_stars">Navigation header image of brawl stars</string>

        <!-- Gadget list item -->
        <string name="image_of_brawlers_gadget">Image of brawlers gadget</string>

        <!-- Fragment profile -->
        <string name="image_of_a_player_icon">Image of a players icon</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_players_experience_level">Image of a players experience level</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_players_total_trophies">Image of a players total trophies</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_player_highest_trophies">Image of a players highest trophies</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_player_highest_power_player_points">Image of a players highest power player points</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_player_three_versus_three_victories">Image of a players three versus three victories</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_player_solo_victories">Image of a players solo victories</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_player_duo_victories">Image of a players duo victories</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_player_best_robo_rumble_time">Image of a players best robo rumble time</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_player_best_time_as_a_big_brawler">Image of a players best time as a big brawler</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_player_championship_qualification">Image of a players championship qualification</string>

        <!-- Fragment brawler details -->
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_icon">Image of a brawlers icon</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_total_trophies">Image of a brawlers total trophies</string>
        <string name="image_model_of_a_brawler">Image model of a brawler</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_highest_trophies">Image of a brawlers highest trophies</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_power_level">Image of a brawlers power level</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_rank">Image of a brawlers rank</string>


    <!-- Clubs list item -->
        <string name="image_of_a_clubs_icon">Image of a clubs icon</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_clubs_total_trophies">Image of a clubs total trophies</string>

        <!-- Brawlers list item -->
        <string name="image_of_a_brawler_list_item">Image of a brawler</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_gadget_list_item">Image of a brawlers gadget</string>
        <string name="image_of_a_brawlers_star_power_list_item">Image of a brawlers star power</string>

        <!-- Activity token login -->
        <string name="image_of_the_apps_logo">Image of the apps logo</string>

        <!-- Fragment home -->
        <string name="image_button_of_a_search_icon">Image button of a search icon</string>


    <!-- Strings for layouts -->

        <!-- Profile list item strings -->
        <string name="trophies_label">Trophies</string>
        <string name="power_label">Power</string>

        <!-- Profile app widget strings -->
        <string name="total_trophies_label">Total trophies</string>
        <string name="update_trophies_label">Update trophies</string>

        <!-- Fragment settings strings -->
        <string name="profile_label">Profile</string>
        <string name="about_label">About</string>
        <string name="rate_the_app_in_google_play_label">Rate the app in Google Play</string>

        <!-- Fragment profile settings strings -->
        <string name="player_tag_label">Player Tag</string>
        <string name="reset_tag_label">Reset Tag</string>
        <string name="player_token_label">Player Token</string>
        <string name="reset_token_label">Reset Token</string>

        <!-- Fragment profile strings -->
        <string name="total_exp_label">Total Exp</string>
        <string name="total_trophies_profile_label">Total Trophies</string>
        <string name="solo_victories_label">Solo Victories</string>
        <string name="duo_victories_label">Duo Victories</string>
        <string name="best_robo_rumble_time_label">Best Robo Rumble Time</string>
        <string name="best_time_as_big_brawler_label">Best Time As Big Brawler</string>
        <string name="champions_qualification_label">Champions Qualification</string>
        <string name="highest_trophies_label">Highest Trophies</string>
        <string name="highest_power_play_points_label">Highest Power Play Points</string>
        <string name="_3_vs_3_victories_label">3 VS 3 Victories</string>

        <!-- Fragment players strings -->
        <string name="rank_label">Rank</string>
        <string name="username_label">Username</string>
        <string name="trophies_player_label">Trophies</string>

        <!-- Fragment clubs strings -->
        <string name="rank_club_label">Rank</string>
        <string name="club_name_label">Club Name</string>
        <string name="trophies_club_label">Trophies</string>

        <!-- Fragment brawler details strings -->
        <string name="highest_trophies_brawler_label">Highest Trophies</string>
        <string name="power_level_label">Power level</string>
        <string name="description_label">Description</string>
        <string name="star_power_label">Star Power</string>
        <string name="gadgets_label">Gadgets</string>
        <string name="brawler_rank_label">rank</string>

    <!-- Activity token login strings -->
        <string name="enter_your_brawl_stars_api_token_label">Enter your brawl stars API token</string>
        <string name="enter_token_label">Enter token</string>
        <string name="go_to_home_label">Go to home</string>
        <string name="don_t_have_a_brawl_stars_token_label">Don\'t have a brawl stars token?</string>
        <string name="click_here_label">Click here!</string>
        <string name="disclaimer">
            Disclaimer \n The app is not accountable for the misuse of a token due to its sole purpose to display brawl star data.</string>
        <string name="brawl_wiki_label">Brawl Wiki</string>

        <!-- Fragment home strings -->
        <string name="enter_your_player_tag_to_view_your_stats_label">Enter Your Player Tag to view your stats:</string>
        <string name="xxxxxxx_label">#XXXXXXX</string>
        <string name="instructions_on_how_to_find_your_tag_label">Instructions on how to find your tag</string>


</resources>